Ha Thi Ninh Giang

Software Engineering student



Personal Profile

I am a Software Engineering student with experience in web development and high interest on AI and Data Science. Please visit my online profile at: My online profile (google.com)

Academic Skills

- Web application development
- Experience in Java, Python, JavaScript & C# programming
- Experience in data visualizing tools & libraries (dash, plotly/matplotlib/ seaborn, Jupyter Notebook, PowerBI, etc.)
- · Basics of machine learning
- Mathematical preliminaries for data science (linear algebra, probability & statistics, multivariable calculus)

Certifications

Foreign Language Certification IELTS Academic 6.5

Academic Standardized tests SAT 1370, SAT Math II 780

VTC Al Practitioner course completion
Certification of course completion

Work Experience

Journalist & Reporter at Press team

Ho Chi Minh Model United Nations | Feb 2017 - Jul 2017

- Create research papers, write articles about global issues
- Work as a reporter at the Model European Union & European Commission

STEAM Teaching Collaborator

Teky Academy | Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

- Instruct children to create 2D games using blockcoding platforms (Tynker & Scratch) and build/develop web using Python + Django framework.
- Prepare detailed reports for every study session

Software Developer Intern

FPT Software | Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

 Explore and implement the file extraction project using COBOL & batch programming, and conduct manual test on a migration project.

Education

High School for the Gifted - VNU HCM

High School Graduation | 2015 - 2018

- Major in Physics
- Excellent Student for 12 school years
- Third prize in the Municipal Excellent Student Contest for High school students in Physics

FPT University - Ho Chi Minh campus

Software Engineering | Class of 2018

- 100% of tuition fee scholarship for full-time study at FPT University
- Top 6 for team performance at SheCodes Hackathon 2020

B2, CODESCO Residential Area, Le Thi Rieng street, Thoi An ward, dist 12, Ho Chi Minh city (+84) 938-868-011 | ninhgiang1502@gmail.com